Preliminary Guide to the Rufus Lusk & Sons business and personal records, 1896-1994 MS2189
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Business records, 1930-1994; Series 1
  - Real estate business records, 1930-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Check stubs, American Security Trust Co [1/2], 1940-1941; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Check stubs, American Security Trust Co [2/2], 1940-1941; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Check stubs, American Security Trust Co. [1/2], 1942-1944; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Check studbs, American Security Trust Co. [2/2], 1942-1944; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence A, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence C, 1941-1963; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence D, 1941-1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence E, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence F, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence Facts Forum, 1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County, VA real estate directory, 1959; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Horn blowing campaign, 1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence J, 1941-1948; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Jefferson Secundus, 1953-1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Kennerly, Jr. J.H. Atlanta Georgia, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Koster monthly reports, 1949-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Charlotte real estate guide answers to questionnaire, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Christmas bonus, 1962, 1965; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 12, Box R1)
      This folder is restricted until 2065.
    - Collection letters (deliquent accounts), 1948-1953; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Attention of Mr. Lusk, Sr., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Correpondence B, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Baltimore City - County sales book, 1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Bank financial statements, 1941-1948; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Business locaiton map, 1948-1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - American Security and Trust Co. financial statements, 1960-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Dunhill list company orders and confirmations, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Dunhill list company orders and confirmations, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Dunhill list company inquiries, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Federal rent control law, 1942; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - General office 149, 1944-1952; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Federal government office building space leased in local buildings, 1940-1942; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - [Real estate directory requests], 1954-1956; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Fulton County real estate guide, Atlanta Georgia, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Housing of World War II veterans and dwelling unit vacancy and occupancy survey - Department of Commerce, 1946; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence G, 1942-1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      Although titled correspondence this folder contains other materials related to office work.
    - Group hospitalization, 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      Lusk employees possible policy.
    - Correspondence L, 1941-1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Littell, Norman N., 1953-1963; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Housing shortage release comments on (January, 1947), 1947 January; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Housing Code Review Committee, 1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Hotel and railroad receipted bills (RSL trips), 1953-1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - 30th Anniversary party, 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams - congratulations, Circa 1940; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence H, 1941-1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Home Builders Association of Metropolitan Washington, 1941-1946; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence K, 1942-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Keane, Michael J. Chevy Chase Circle Community Center, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Form letters 1951 apartment directory, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Form letters Montgomery County, Md. Real estate directory, 1947-1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Form letters Northern Virginia real estate guide, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Form letters Northern Virginia real estate guide, 1951, 1958; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Form letters 1958 D.C. zoning map, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Form letters 1951 D.C. zoning map, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Work sheets, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Letters answered, 1963-1964; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Letters attention RSL Sr. and RSL Jr., 1962-1964; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - [papers, no title], 1951-1953; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Survey of Insurance, 1958 January 14; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence I, 1941-1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Income tax returns, 1943-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Housing, 1942-1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Income tax returns, 1930-1943; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Lobbying act, 1948-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence R, T, 1944; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Time, Inc. February 1954 mailing - T9045, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Directory material Pittsburgh, PA, 1949-1953; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Fitz S. Hofheimer (correspondence and lists), 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Fitz S. Hofheimer (correspondence and lists), 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - [Directory data], 1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence W, 1942; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Dunhill List Company Herbert G. Odza, 1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Mailings, inc., 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Mailings, inc. orders, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Dickey - Raymond D. - R. special list, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - William F. Rupert birth lists, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Hill, Robert L. landlord, 1947-1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Speeches made by Rufus S. Lusk, 1943; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Jefferson Secundus, 1948-1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      Jefferson Secundus is a cat.
    - Photographs Rufus S. Lusk, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Press Club dinners, 1936, 1939; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Newsweek mailing, 1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Lease negotiations, 1824026 Jefferson Place, N.W., 1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda - J M L, 1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Guides - miscellaneous memoranda, 1967-1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - News releases - general, 1967-1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence Russsell L. Bigelow, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Code Numbers, list of, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Code Calls, record of, 1954-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Mimeographed memoranda mailing prospects, 1965; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Beach recordings, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Virginia Beach, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Residential mortgage recordings in Reston Virginia for the past three years, 1968-1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Reggie Jones - Richmond Virginia, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Study of mortgage recordings for Dominion Bankshares Corporation, 1971-1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 1st Federal Savings and Loan job, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Odenton Savings and Loan mtf. Job, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - People's Savings and Loan study, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Equitable Savings and Loan Assn. statistical study, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Richmond Federal Savings and Loan mtg job, 1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Capitol Building and Loan Assn. job (Richmond), 1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Capitol Building and Loan Assn. job (Richmond), 1966-1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Dominion Bankshares Corporation, 1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Wolftrappe Savings and Loan Assn. Vienna, Va., P. Daniel, 1973-1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - People's Savings and Loan Assn. of Virginia Beach, 1973-1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Residential mortgage recordings in Fairfax County, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - A study of mortgage recordings prepared for Annapolis Federal Savings and Loan Assn., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - A study of mortgage recordings in the 6th, 9th, 12th, and 15th, Election District of P.G. County, Md. Prepared for Annapolis Federal Savings and Loan Assn., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - A study of first mortgage recordings on residential property in Virginia Beach, 1975-1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - City of Baltimore residential mortgage recordings $40,000 and under, 1967-1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Check disbursement and payroll records, 1954-1956, 1958; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 24, Box R2, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 1)
      The content of this folder is restricted. The four folders in the restricted box (R2) are all represented in box 67 as being in folder 24.
    - City of Baltimore residential mortgage recordings $40,000 and under, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Residential mortgage recordings in Fairfax County, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Alexandria property survey, 1958-1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - City of Baltimore residential mortgage recordings $40,000 and under, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Study of mortgage recordings for Metropolitan Richmond, Va., 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Lusknet II online system user manual, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Lusk's Northern Virginia real estate directory service, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Beach mortgage survey People's Savings and Loan, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1992 Map royalty report on the accural basis, 1993 January 19; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Map royalty computation on a cash basis for the State of Maryland Department of Assessment and Taxation, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Map royalty computation on a cash basis for the State of Maryland Department of Assessment and Taxation, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Management by objectives, 1984-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Maps - Balto Co. [Baltimore County], 1986-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Maps - Carroll County, 1988-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Maps - DC, 1986-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Maps - Fairfax County, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Maps - Montgomery County, 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Mortgage data studies, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - National Association of Realtors (statistical studies), 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Memos, 1980-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Monopolistic considerations, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Marketing research, 1979-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Maps - MD state [1/4], 1991-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Maps - MD state [2/4], 1989-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Maps - MD state [3/4], 1990-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Maps - MD state [4/4], 1985-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Newspapers, 1980-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Northern Virginia Board of Realtors, 1986-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - MLS - NoVa [Northern Virginia], 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Prince George's weekly survey, 1983 August 1; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - MLS - PG [Prince Georges], 1980-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Mailing labels, 1984-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Mailing list - Citicorp, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Mailing list - MNB [Maryland National Bank], 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery County government reports, 1980-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery County apartment directory, 1980-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Montgomery County Board of Realtors, 1979-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery County and Prince Georges County economic reports, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Mortgage quotes, 1980-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Office building directory promotion, 1982-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Office building directory survey, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - On-line planning conference marketing, 1982-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Open house, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Prince George's County Board of Realtors, 1979-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Office matters, 1979-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Quotes - printing [1/2], 1988-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Quotes - printing [2/2], 1979-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Plus and minus statements, 1970-1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - News releases - services, 1963-1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 1955 DC Real Estate Directory, 1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Antitrust marketing considerations, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta guide and directory cost analysis paper, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Carroll County Directory, 1981-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Cash flow analysis (Rufus S. Lusk, III), 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Corporation sponsored parties, 1968-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Correspondents, 1965-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - DC real estate assessment clippings, Circa 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Nassau realty statistics, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Opinion survey DC Real Estate Services, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Suffolk public record Mrs. Grace F. Davis, Publisher, 1973-1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Sanborn map company, 1974-1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Property transfers in England and Ireland, 1963; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Letters - miscellaneous, 1940-1942; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - House, 1941; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Gallwey, T.H.E. Waterford, Ireland, 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Foreign taxation, 1956; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - ADS Baltimore City, 1983-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - ADS Baltimore County, 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - ADS - Carroll County, 1987-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Advertising Baltimore, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - ADS Arlington County, 1987-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Advertising Anne Arundel County, 1987-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper articles, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - ADS - DC [District of Columbia], 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Appraisers brochure, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Negatives of display photographs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Flyers, Silver Spring office, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Lusk News in Baltimore area, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Compaign Lusk response to CMMLS "Crabnet", 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - ADS Baltimore (color), undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Lusknet II user guide, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - LuskNews, 1994 Winter; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Old ads, 1986-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Lusk Map News [newsletter], 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - RSLIII deposition [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 August 6; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits 1-8 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Exhibits 9-18 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit 18 (cont.) [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits 19-53 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits 54-92 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      Please note: Exhibits 69-70 are in box 91.
    - Exhibit 69 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit] [1/2], Circa 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Exhibit 69 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit] [2/2], Circa 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Exhibit 70 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits 93-108 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits 109-127, Circa 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits 128-133 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Dator PR [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit] [1/2], 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Dator PR [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit] [2/2], 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Michael Jacobson depo day 1 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 September 27; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Michael Jacobson depo day 2 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 October 1; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Michael Jacobson depo day 3 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 October 6; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Michael Jacobson / Dator [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Target marketing network file [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - TMN target marketing network [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Litigation documents pages 477-606 [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], Circa 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Lusk/Dator data service agreement [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1990-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Don Sabatini tape log [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 July 19; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Claude Fuchs Dator / react file [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1991-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Lusk record layouts [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Lusk document production Carol Burch Stewart documents [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Lusk document production general [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1990-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Lusk tape delivery [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1993 May 25; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - James H. Molloy, Jr. file [Dator vs. Lusk lawsuit], 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - NOVA: we know where you live [VHS], 1990 November 27; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - D.C. Flat Directory, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Transfer, 1965-1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - DeKalb County Guide, 1965-1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Douglas County Guide, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Fulton County Directory, 1965-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Athens and Clarke County, Ga., 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Charlotte and Mecklenberg County Guide, 1964-1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Clayton County Guide, 1969-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Clayton County, Ga. Directory, 1973-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Cobb County Guide, 1963-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Cobb County Directory, 1963-1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - DeKalb County Directory, 1968-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Fulton County Guide, 1963-1972; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Gwinnett County Guide, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Gwinnett County Directory, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Montgomery Transfer, 1967; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Nashville Directory, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Nashville Guide, 1965-1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Interview with Dell Christy re: working for Rufus Lusk Sr. In 1940, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Housing an Home Finance Agency, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - DC Line, 1992 March; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      This is a Lusk publication.
    - In Search of Wholeness, 1977 October; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Lusk Fall 1984 Planning Conference, 1984 October 11 -13; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Washington Business Review, 1938, 1948; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Washington Housing Shortage A Myth?, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Receipts, 1895-1897; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 15)